previously on...
剧情回顾
well,if libby here likes us as much as we like her,
好的，如果Libby能像我们喜欢她那样 喜欢我们喜欢我们
we should just go ahead and move to adopt her baby girl.
我们应该直接去收养她的小女孩
Who's the father?
谁是父亲？
Honestly,I don't know.
说实话，我不知道
Carlos and gaby made a deal...
Carlos和Gaby达成了一致
I did remarry my ex,but it was only because he has great health insurance.
我是和我的前夫复婚 但那只是因为他有不错的健康保险
Susan made amends...
Susan道了歉
you know,I never thoughtI'd have such a good time
你知道，我从没有想过我会如此开心
hanging out with my girlfriendand her husband.
和我的女朋友及她的丈夫一起出去
And mike...
而Mike...
didn't she mention we dated?
她有没有说过我们以前曾经在一起？
Made a confession...
作了坦白……
liar! You've just beenleading me on!
你骗我！你一直在欺骗我的感情！
You're obviously still in lovewith this guy!
你显然还爱着这个家伙！
Of his own.
对他自己作了坦白
On her first day of sobriety,
在她戒酒的第一天
bree van de kamp found an old cork,
Bree Van De Kamp发现了一个旧木塞
which reminded her just how much she craved chablis.
提醒了她自己是多么想要喝酒
So she called her sponsor,who came over with a dvd
于是她打电话找人来帮忙 他带来了一盘DVD
which they watched till her craving had passed.
他们一直看着DVD直到她的渴望慢慢退去
Five days later,after she developed a thirst for merlot,
5天后，她想喝Merlot酒的时候
peter arrived with a deck of cards.
Peter带来了一副牌
The next week,he brought over chinese takeout because bree ad told him
又过了一周，他带来了中国菜的外卖 因为Bree告诉他
she was consumed by thoughts of vintage chardonnay.
自己很想喝夏敦埃酒
By her 20th day of sobriety,bree had stopped thinking about alcohol altogether
在她戒酒的第20天 Bree不再想要喝酒了
because her thoughts were now centered elsewhere.
因为她的思绪围绕了一些别的东西
I'm curious,peter.What is the easiest way to overcome addiction?
我很好奇，Peter 克服上瘾的最简单的方法是什么？
Oh,some folkstry shock therapy.Other use,hypnosis.
有人说是冲击疗法，也有人说是催眠
But taking it one dayat a time still makes the most sense to me.
但我觉得一天天慢慢来更有效
Why?
怎么？
I don't know.I guess I'm just impatientto get on with my life.
不知道，可能我对生活缺乏耐性
What are you doing?
干嘛？
I was justgiving you a little kiss.
我只是轻轻的亲你一下
Why?
为什么？
Well,it's just my wayof saying thank you
嗯，我已这种方式来感谢你
for everything you've donefor me over the past few weeks.
为了过去的几周里你为我做的一切
What'S... wrong?
有什么不对吗？
This is gonna seem likeit's coming out of left field,
这看起来好像有点越线了
but in addition to beinga recovering alcoholic,I'm also a member of S.A.
除了是一名康复中的酗酒者之外 我也是S.A.的一员
Sex addicts anonymous.
性爱互助者协会
And that's A...a real thing?
你是说--是说真的？
Yes. Sex is as muchan addiction for me as booze.
是的，性和酒一样会使我上瘾
That's why whenyou turn me on like that,it's a bit of a problem.
如果你挑逗我，后果很严重
It was justa peck on the cheek.
我只是亲吻你的脸
It doesn't matter.The slightest touchgets my juices flowing.
一点触碰都会让我春情泛滥
So... how long has it been since you--
那么...你有多久没有--？
a year.
一年
They have this rule--plant,pet,person.
都是这样的--从植物到宠物，再到人
If I can keepa plant alive,you know,then I can move on to a pet.
如果可以养活植物 就可以去养宠物
And if I can make that work,then I can start dating again.
如果可以养好宠物 那就可以再次开始约会
so how are you doing?
所以你做的怎样？
I'm on my fourth ficus.
我在养第四棵ficus了 （注：ficus是一种热带植物）
see?
看见了吗？
I think you can handle affection better than you give yourself credit for.
我想你能处理好男女关系的 而不是像别人说的那么糟糕
I'm sorry.
对不起
I think I should go.
-我想我该走了
Peter! But--but...you forgot your shirt!
Peter！但是…… 你忘了拿衬衫了！
Keep it.
你留着吧
Though she didn't know it,bree had answered her own question.
虽然她自己不知道 但是Bree已经回答了她自己的问题
The easiest way to overcome one addiction...
克服上瘾最简单的方法...
is to replace it with another.
就是让自己对另外一样东西上瘾
Temptation--
“诱惑”
it's the name  of a well-known establishment on the outskirts of fairview.
是一家在市郊很著名的公司的名字
Its clientele is devoted.
它的客户都很投入
Everyone who goes there wants to get their hands on something.
每个去那里的人都想 把自己的手放在一些东西上
And when they cross a line...
当他们越线时……
I warned you,pal.
我警告过你，伙计
They are punished...
他们就会遭受惩罚……
as a certain married couple were about to discover.
就像一对已婚夫妇将会发现
You want a lap dance?
你想要个贴身舞吗？
no,thanks. No.
不，谢谢，不
I sure hope libby likes this camera.
我希望Libby喜欢这个摄像机
Well,why wouldn't she?It's exactly what she asked for,
好吧，怎么会不喜欢？她正是她要的
the most expensive one in the store.
商店里面最贵的
You know,I'm telling you,carlos.
跟你说，Carlos
I'm getting really tired of kissing her ass.
我真的对于一直排她马屁感到厌烦了
The woman is giving us her baby.
这个女人将要把她的孩子给我们
We'll kiss whatever needs kissing.
马屁怎么拍都行！
What the hell are you guys doing here?
你们在这里干什么？
Uh,we brought you this gift,
嗯，我们带了这个礼物给你
and you said that you didn't want us coming by your house...
你说你不想我们到你家去
thanks,but I'm working,so you gotta go.
谢谢，但是我在工作，所以你们快点走吧
Look,we spent a lot of money on that.
看，我们为这个花了很多钱
The least you can do is open it so we can bask in your happy expression.
你至少应该打开它 让我们看看你开心的表情
Is there a problem here?
有什么问题吗？
No,we're just talking.It's--everything's fine.
不，我们只是谈谈，没事
Carlos solis.This is my wife,gabrielle.
我是Carlos Solis 这是我太太，Gabrielle
We're friends of libby'S.
我们是Libby的朋友
Oh,hey,I'm frank,libby's boyfriend.
哦，我叫Frank，我是Libby的男友
Libby,you didn't tell us you had a boyfriend.
Libby，你没有告诉我们你有个男友
Didn't I?I thought I had.
没有吗？我以为说了
What's that,a present for our baby?
那是什么，给我们孩子的礼物？
I'm sorry,did you just say "our" baby?
对不起，你刚才是不是说“我们的”孩子？
It's our first.
是的，这是我们第一个孩子
What's for lunch?
嗨，午饭吃什么？
Omelettes. You want me to make you one?
菜肉蛋卷，要再给你做一份吗？
No,thank you.I'll just pick at yours.
不，谢谢，我吃点你的就行了
I didn't know you still had a key,dad.
我不知道你还有一把钥匙，爸爸
Of course I do.
当然有
I have to watch out for my two favorite ladies.
我要照看我最中意的两位女士
Try the cheese.That's the best part.
尝尝奶酪，最好吃的就是这个
You mean,two of your three favorite ladies.
你是说，你最中意的三位女士中的两位
You know,when you add in edie.
你和Edie在一起
Right! Of course.And speaking of edie,I have some big news.
对！当然，说到Edie，我有一些大新闻
I finally did it.I popped the question.
我终于说了，我向她求婚了
Congratulations,dad!
恭喜，爸爸！
Yeah... congratulations.
是的...恭喜！
what happened to waiting six months?
六个月之后会发生什么？
edie and I aren't getting married tomorrow.
Edie和我不会明天就结婚
It takes months to plan a classy wedding,you know?
准备一场上等的婚礼 需要几个月，你知道？
Remember ours,hmm? You had to have it outdoors?
记得我们的婚礼吗？你非要在室外举行？
It poured.I could have murdered that weatherman.
那天倾盆大雨 我应该杀了那个天气预报员
we were all crammed under this little gazebo thingy.
我们都挤在露台的下面
It was hysterical.I thought the whole wedding day was ruined.
我当时快气疯了 我觉得整个婚礼都被毁掉了
I loved it!
我喜欢！
It felt spontaneous.
那感觉很自然
All our friends gathered close around us?
我们所有的朋友都挤在我们周围？
Remember?
记得吗？
You said it was the happiest day of your life.
你说那是你一生中最开心的一天
just like you marrying edie will be the happiest day of her life.
就像你娶Edie的那天 也会成为她一生中最开心的一天
Right.
对
Her,too.
她也会很开心的
Andrew said it was all right for me to get a cream soda.
Andrew说我可以拿一个苏打冷饮
Uh,sure. Help yourself.
嗯，当然可以，请便
There's also frosted glasses in the freezer.
冰箱里还有结霜的杯子
Can is fine,but thank you.
易拉罐就可以了，不过，还是谢谢你
I left a list for you of the witnesses we'll be deposing.
我给你留了一张单子 我们将要作证的证人
It's,there on the counter.
就在台子上
I know that you're still angry with me,and,
我知道你还在生我的气
I wanted to tell you that I have,joined a recovery program.
告诉你，我已经参加了个戒酒课程，A.A （A.A.是嗜酒者互诫协会的缩写）
I just wanted you to know that...
我只是想跟你说这事情
and to tell you I'm sorry.
还有跟你说对不起
You are...
你是……
a real friend,and I value your honesty.
一个真正的朋友，我很在乎你的诚实
Oh,I don't wannabe mad anymore.
哦，我不想再发火了
and I'm so happyto hear all that,and I am so proud of you.
我很高兴听到这些，我非常为你骄傲
thanks,but I'm not reallyout of the woods yet.
谢谢，但是我还是没有完全摆脱麻烦
I still have this wholecourt case hanging over my head.
我还是有一桩法庭的案子在烦我
I heard about that.Andrew's askingto be emancipated?
我听说了，Andrew提出要脱离监管？
Yes,and his lawyeris taking depositions now to see if I am a fit parent.
是的，他的律师正在调查取证 来看看我是不是一个合适的母亲
And considering that mishapthat I had with your kids,
考虑到那次我和你孩子之间的事故
I,uh,I imaginehe'll be anxious to talk to you.
嗯，我想他会急迫地想要和你谈话
Well,it makes sense,I guess.
由这可能，我觉得
Do you have any idea what you might say?
你想过准备说些什么吗？
I,I'll focuson your good qualities.
我，我会集中说你的优点
I could not ask for anything more.
我不能再奢求更多了
Thanks.
谢谢
See you around,I hope.
- 回头见
All right.
没问题
That'S... not why you came to apologize,is it?
那不是……你来道歉的原因，是吧？
What do you mean?
这是什么意思？
To soften me upfor the deposition.
为了作证的事情，来向我求情
of course not.
当然不是
I just want youto understand something.
我只是想让你了解一些事情
Andrew ismaking accusations--
Andrew在提出指控——
false accusations,saying that I abused him,
错误的指控，说我虐待他
all because I wouldn't let him have his trust fund early so he could buy a car.
因为我不肯让他提前 拿到信托基金买车
I mean,can you blame mefor wanting to know if I have your support?
你可以因为我想知道你是不是支持我 而责怪我吗？
And...so... what,
那...又...怎么样？
you want me to lie?Make you look good?
你想让我说谎？帮你掩饰？
I actually don't wantanything of the sort.
我不是想要你做这种事
Good.
好
Because when I give my deposition,I'm goingto tell the truth.
因为在我作证的时候，我会说出真相
to what do I owethis pleasure?
什么风把你吹来了啊？
I want youto look at something.
我想让你看一些东西
Myra holtis talking to paul young,
Myra Holt在和Paul Young谈话
chatting away with him as thoughhe were any other neighbor.
就像和普通邻居一样的和他聊天
Now I told herhe killed my sister.
我告诉过她，他杀死了我的姐姐
I mentioned it to hersix months ago when we were
我六个月前就对她提过
standing in the express lineat the market.
就在我们在超市结帐的时候
But still,there she is,yakking away.
但是她仍然在和他聊天
Oh,mike.I'm afraid people's memoriesaren't what they used to be.
Mike，恐怕人们的记忆已经不如从前了
What do you want,felicia?
你想怎么样，Felicia？
I wanna seehow good your memory is,
我想看看你的记忆力怎么样
if you recall a certain promiseyou made to me.
你还记得你发过的誓言吗？
I am not gonna kill him.
我不会杀他的
Why not?Give me one good reason.
为什么？给我一个好理由
Becausethings have changed.
因为事情变了
How? My sister still liesrotting in the ground.
怎么变了？我的姐姐仍然躺在地下
So does dierdre. No,I don't seehow anything's changed at all.
Dierdre也一样 我根本没有看到任何事情改变了
You're just gonnahave to let this go.
你不得不让这事情就这样了结
Sounds to me as thoughsomeone's let go of his rage.
听起来某些人好像已经不再愤怒了
Maybe I have.
也许是的
Well,i haven'T.
但是我没有
The father'stotally in the dark.
小孩父亲根本就什么都不知道
He clearly wants to keep the baby
他显然想要留住孩子
.Mr. Solis,if the father wants to assert his rights here,there's nothing we can do.
Solis先生，如果孩子父亲不同意 我们就没办法了
I'll find you another baby.I promise.
我保证，我会替你们再找一个
I don't want another baby.I want this one!
我不想要别的孩子，我就想要这个！
Oh,honey,he's right,okay.
哦，甜心，他说得对
That trashy girl has beenlying to us from the get-go.
那个垃圾似的女人一开始就在说谎
Let's just walk awaywhile we can. It's not worth it.
趁着还来得及，我们可以再找 （盯着一个）那样做不值得
Look,don't get cold feet now,gaby,please. All right?
看，别现在就灰心 Gaby，拜托，好吗？
Let's just pay frankthe way we paid libby and then
让我们就像收买Libby那样收买Frank
bring the baby home.
- 然后把孩子带回家。
Wait,wait,wait...
等等，等等...
you paid libby?
你们给Libby钱了？
You saidwe could give her gifts.Everybody loves getting cash.
你说我们可以给她礼物的,人人都喜欢钱
I could probably be disbarredfor even listening to this.
就是听听这个 我也有可能被剥夺律师资格
I cannot condone baby-buying!
我不能容忍买卖婴儿！
And I sure as hellcan't be part of it.
我更不能参与其中
Oh,mr. Beale,come on.
哦，Beale先生，别这样
No,no,hear me out.
不，不，听我说
If you are determinedto go down this dark road,and unbeknownst to mesteal this...
如果你们决定一意孤行， 并在我不知道的情况下，拿走...
paternal rights waiverthat's sitting on my desk,
我桌子上的这份父亲弃权声明书
and have this frank guy signboth sides and date the top,
并让那个叫Frank的在两面签名 写上日期
I can't be part of that,either.
这种事情，我也不能参与
Okay,I-I'm gonnago to dad'S.
好的，我，我会去爸爸那里的
Oh,wait! Why don'tyou let me walk with you?
哦，等等！为什么不让我和你一起去呢？
Uh,shouldn't yoube resting?
嗯，你不是应该多休息吗？
No! I'm fine.
不！我没事
The doctor said I should actually keep my blood flowing.
医生说我应该保持血液循环
Well,do you have to do it whilewe walk over to edie's?
你非得在要我们去Edie那里的时候陪我吗？
I just... I don't wanna riskyou running into dad.
我只是...我怕你碰到爸爸
Okay...
好的...
you guys havejust been so chummy lately,
你们最近总是很亲密
and... this whole flirting thingis kind of freaking me out.
而且...这种调情的事情把我吓坏了
Wait a second,we're--we're not flirting.
等一等，我们，我们没有调情
Mom,you fed him eggswith your fork.
妈妈，你用自己的叉子喂他鸡蛋
Okay,yes,I am closer to your father than I have been in the past.
好吧，是的，我和你 父亲比过去亲近了一点
The bitter hatred's now settledinto a respectful disgust.
那痛苦的憎恨现在变成了有礼貌的厌恶
That's the kind of thing most children of divorce dream about.
那时很多离婚家庭的孩子梦寐以求的
Hey,edie.What's all this stuff for?
嗨，Edie， 这些东西是用来干什么的？
Oh,hi!Don't tell anyone,but I'm planninga huge surprise for karl.
哦，嗨！不要告诉别人， 我正在为karl准备一个大惊喜
A surprise?
惊喜？
Yeah,I'm putting togetheran engagement party tomorrow afternoon.
是的，我要在明天下午办一个订婚派对
Oh,cool. But that's notthe surprise.
哦，酷，但那不是惊喜
Actually,it's gonna bea surprise wedding.
事实上，那会是一个惊喜的婚礼
I know!My pilates teachergot ordained over the internet.
我知道！我在网上任命了牧师
The,uh,church of the divinesomething or other.
嗯，神圣的教堂或是别的什么
I'm not sure.Anyway,it's all legal.
我也不知道，无论如何 这一切都是合法的
And,well,just one more day before I make an honest manout of your daddy.
就在一天前我接受了你父亲的求婚
You're so sweet.Thank you so much for your good wishes.
你真好，谢谢你的祝福
Oh. No,edie,wait.Um,no,it's just that...
哦，不，Edie，等等，嗯，只是...
you know,I was married to karl,and I used to...
你知道，我曾经嫁给Karl，我过去……
try to surprise him,and he would always,always,always say...
一直试图去给他惊喜， 他总是，总是，总是会说……
"no,susan. Don't surprise me.I don't like it."
“不，Susan。 不要给我惊喜，我不喜欢”
Whatever. I'm doing it,so keep your trap shut.
不管怎样，我都要干 所以还是收起你那一套
Now if you'll excuse me,I've gotta go and buya wedding dress.
现在如果你不介意的话 我要去买婚纱了
Oh,and by the way,I'll be wearing white,
哦，顺便说一句，我会穿白色的婚纱
so that'll be a surprisefor everybody.
所以那将对所有人来说都是一个惊喜
I don't know whyI have to get dragged into this.
我不知道我怎么会牵扯到这件事情中的
What happened with my kids
发生在我孩子身上的事情
has nothing to do withbree's situation with andrew.Sit.
和Bree与Andrew的情况没有关系，坐
Well,it's my understanding
在我看来
that real harm could havecome to your children
你的孩子们可能真的会受到伤害
as a direct resultof your friend's behavior.
因为你的朋友的行为
I'm sorry,mr. Bormanis,but I'm not gonna testify.
对不起，Bormanis先生 但是我不会作证的
It justdoesn't feel right to me.
那样让我感觉不好
Well,this isn't the first timesomeone's felt the way you do.
好吧，你的这种情况不是第一次
So this isn't the first timeI've had to say that
所以这也不是我第一次不得不这么说
if you refuse to givea deposition of your own accord,
如果你拒绝自愿作证
I'll compel youto give one.
我会强迫你作证的
but I'm sureI won't have to.
但是我肯定我不必这么干
You're sayingbree did this?
你说这是bree干的？
While under the influence.
在外界影响下
I understand your reluctanceto turn on a friend,but this isn't about you.
我明白你为了维护朋友不愿作证 但是这不是关于你的事情
It's about andrew.
这是关于andrew的事情
Don't you thinkhe's suffered enough?
你不认为他已经受够苦了吗？
How muchare you gonna give him?
你要给他多少？
I figuredwe could start with forty.
我认为我们可以从4万开始
Thousand?
4万？
He's a bouncer in a strip club.Offer him eight.
他是脱衣舞场里的保镖。给他8千
He's not goingto sell his baby for $8,000.
他不会为了8千就把孩子卖了的
Are we talking aboutthe same idiot?
我们说的是同一个白痴吗？
I think for $8,000,you throw in a kidney.
我认为8千就够了
I'm not gonna blow thisby bargain hunting.
我不会抱着捡便宜货的心态 去办这件事情的
You know,that's your problem,carlos.
你知道，那是你的问题，carlos
Remember when you boughtyour car? You paid sticker.Nobody pays sticker!
记得你买车的时候吗？你买了滞销品 没有人会买滞销品的
Okay,and what's the stickerprice on a child,huh?
okay，那什么是一个 滞销的孩子的价钱，huh？
Tell me that.
-告诉我
I'm thinking $12,000.
我想12000够了
Frank,you have to sign the paper.I made a deal with these people.
frank，你必须签了它 我和这些人有协议
A deal?
协议？
This isn't a used car we'retalking about. It's our baby.
我们讨论的不是一辆二手车 是我们的孩子
Before you screw this up,
在你搞砸前
just remember that I cango to the cops and tell them
记住我可以去告诉警察
about the pot farm you havegoing on in our basement.
你在我们的地下室有个大麻农场
it's justa couple plants.
那只是一些植物
Yeah,I don't do it for profits.
yeah，我不是为了钱才干的
Hobby,mostly.
基本上是兴趣
Oh,come on,frank. You knowyou would be a lousy father.
oh，得了吧，frank 你知道你会一个糟糕的父亲
It's my kid! And I have a rightto mess her up if I want.
这是我的孩子！我有权利 把她弄得一塌糊涂，只要我想
And if you go near the police,
如果你去找警察
I'll tell 'em how you've been stealingall those tips from sheila.
我会告诉他们你是怎样 从sheila那里偷来这些东西的
okay,we're done.
okay，我们完事了
Gaby,gaby,no,just...hold on.
Gaby，gaby，不，就……等一会儿
Now maybe there's a way that we can work this out together.
现在我们也许可以找到解决事情的方法
There is nothingto work out.
没有什么好解决的
If frank is not on boardwith this,it's over.
如果frank不参与的话，这件事情就完了
Wait! Uh...it doesn't matter what he wants.
等等！嗯……他怎么想无关紧要
Why not?
为什么？
Becauseit's not your baby.
因为这不是你的孩子
That's a lie.
你在说谎
What if I took a paternity test?Will that shut you up?
我要不要去做个亲子鉴定？ 那样可不可以让你闭嘴？
Wait,if it's not frank's,then whose is it?
等等，如果这不是frank的孩子 那这孩子是谁的？
I'm not sure.All's I know is,
我不知道。我只知道
I got pregnant right afterI worked at the calgary rodeo,
我在calgary rodeo 工作后不久就怀孕了
and I was very popular there.
我在那里很受欢迎
So what are you saying,you screwed a bunch of cowboys?
你在说什么？你跟一群牛仔鬼混？
You have your hobbies..and I have mine.
你有你的爱好……我也有我的
you think this is funny?
你认为这很有趣？
Oh,don't you get it?
哦，你还不明白？
We just got our baby back.
我们有可以得到那个孩子了
well,you take care now.
好吧，你自己当心
I got,uh,your message that you wanted to see mebefore the meeting started.
我收到了，嗯，你的留言 说你想在开会前见见我
Yeah,I did. Um,there's someoneI'd like to introduce you to.
对，我留言了 我想介绍个人给你认识
Bree,this is donna.
bree，这是donna
Donna,this is bree.
-donna，这是bree
What's up?
你好
Donna is gonna beyour new sponsor.
donna会使你的新伙伴
I,um,I don't wanta new sponsor.
我，um，我不想要新伙伴
I'M... I'm very comfortableworking with you.
我……我对于和你一起合作感到很舒服
Look,this was alwaysjust a temporary arrangement.
看，这只是一个临时的安排
And given what happenedthe other night,
考虑到那晚发生的事情
I think it's bestif we just end this now.
我想我们最好还是现在结束
Peter,all we did was kiss.
peter，我们只不过接吻而已
we'd be kidding ourselvesif we didn't think that
我们只是在欺骗自己，如果我们认为
whatever's between us isn'tgoing to affect our recovery.
我们之间的事情不会影响我们的康复
It's not a good timefor change in my life,peter.
peter，现在对我来说 不是一个变化的好时候
Terrible things are happening.I'm headed to court.
可怕的事情在发生。我要去法院出庭
I need your supportnow more than ever.
我现在比任何时候都需要你的支持
You'll have support,bree.
bree，你会得到支持的
It just won't be mine.
只是不再是我的支持罢了
But,peter...
但是，peter……
oh,bree could neverhave done that!
oh，bree绝对不会这么干的！
I'm just telling youwhat the lawyer said.
我只是告诉你那个律师说的话
So you think breepunched andrew in the face?'Cause I don'T.
那么你认为bree打了andrew的脸？ 因为我不这么想
I don't either,but on the other hand,
我也不相信，但是另一方面来说
she spanked my kids,she lied about her drinking
她打过我的孩子，她对她酗酒的事情说谎
and I once saw her bitch slapher mother-in-law.
有一次我还看到她骂她的婆婆
So I'm torn.
所以我很迷惑
Well,I'm siding with bree.
我站在bree这一边
How can you be so sure?
你怎么会这么肯定？
We have andrew saying thatit's systematic physical abuse.
andrew说这是有计划的肉体虐待
And thenwe have bree saying it's andrewwanting to be emancipated
那bree还说这是andrew想要脱离监管
so he can get at his trust fundso he can buy a car.
那样他就可以得到他的信托基金 可以买一辆车
How are we supposed to knowthe real truth?
我们怎么知道什么才是真相？
BecauseI remember being 17.
因为我记得我17岁时
And I would've donea hell of a lot more than punch myself in the eyeto get a car.
为了得到一辆车，我会做出 比打肿我的脸更加极端的事情
Karl!
karl！
Karl,stop! Stop!
karl，停下！停下！
Oh! It's an emergency.
oh！这事情很紧急
Just calm down.What's going on?
冷静。到底怎么啦？
Edie is gonna marry you tomorrow.
edie会在明天嫁给你
What?
什么？
She's plannedthis whole secret wedding.It's a surprise.
她策划了整个秘密婚礼。这是一个惊喜
God,I hate surprises!
天啊，我讨厌惊喜！
I know. I told her that.
我知道。我告诉过她
I said,"he always,always hates surprises."
我说，“他一直，一直讨厌惊喜。”
All right,don't get yourselfall worked up here.
好吧，不要站在这里说
So the thingyou gotta know about me is my style is proactive.
你应该了解, 我通常未雨绸缪 (喝酒前给予劝说)
I don't hold your handif you go on a bender.
而在你喝酒之时我是我不会阻止你的
I believein behavior modification.
我相信行为的自我矫正
Hmm. Some muffins?
嗯 来些松饼吗?
Oh. Oh,that's okay.I-I'm not big on snacks.
好吧 不过我不太爱吃点心
You should also know...
你也该了解...
I'm not a lesbian.
我不是女同性恋
Oh!
噢!
Well,good for you.
那很好啊
Well,see,if I was,the programwouldn't let me be your sponsor.
如果我是 协会不可能让我当你的互助伙伴的
Not greatfor your recovery if we get tangled upin a little somethin'.
如果我俩有点“纠缠”的话 对你的康复不利
So,um,
那么...
whatever vibeyou might be getting, that's all on you.
你会变成怎样全在乎你自己
Um,donna...
Donna...
I-I really appreciate everything
我真的很感激
that you've been doing for me,
你为我所做的这些事
but I think I was reallymaking some progress
但我认为Peter作为我的互助伙伴期间
with peter as my sponsor.
我的戒酒治疗的确有很大进展
And I was thinking--
我也在想--
all right,stop right there!
够了 打住!
You're fixating on peter.
看来你很在意Peter啊
Well,I just really feel likeI'm jeopardizing my recovery by switching--
我只是认为更换互助伙伴 对我的康复很不利
you're making excuses.
你在编借口罢了
See,I have a 99% success rateas a sponsor
作为互助伙伴, 我极其成功
because I have 0% tolerance for peoplewho lie to themselves.
因为我对那些对自己撒谎的人 一点都不宽容
Now come on.
那好吧
Come on?Where are we going?
好吧? 我们去哪?
Hiking.
远足
There's nothing like itto take your mind off booze.
没有比它更能转移你对酒的兴趣的事了
I got it!
我知道怎么说了
I'll just be the woman.I'll say I want a big wedding.
像女人们常说的那样 我会说我想要一个盛大的婚礼
You know,the church,the big ballroom,
你知道的 教堂, 跳舞场地
smushing cake in her face--it'll take months to plan.
把蛋糕抹在她脸上-- 这些需要准备好几个月
That's great.
很好啊
And of course,I'll have to tell her you're the onewho ruined the surprise.
当然了, 我会告诉她破坏惊喜的人是你
You're gonnamake me take the hit?
你想让我承担主要责任?
Yeah.
是的
Hey,guys.What you doing out here?
你们好啊 在外面干什么呢
Uh,just talking.
随便聊聊
Oh,well,come on in.I've got something to show you.
噢, 进来吧 我想让你们看些东西
Oh,no,that's okay.
哦, 不用了吧
Come on!You'll love this.
进来吧 你们会喜欢的
wait until I leave to tell her, 'cause she's gonna kill me.
等我走了再告诉她 因为她知道以后肯定会杀了我
Well,I should go.
我该走了
I'm not gonna scream or cry
我不会尖叫或者哭泣
or pound your faces inwith a mallet,
或者拿槌棒痛打你们的脸
which,lord knows,is my right.
--尽管这些都是我的权利
But what I will sayis that you two are the most
但我必须得说, 你们两个
reprehensible excuses for human beings that I have ever met!
犯下了这世界上最不可饶恕的罪过
Do you have anythingto add?
有什么要补充的吗?
Right.
很好
What the hell.
滚蛋吧
Oh! Get out! Get--
噢! 快走
Hey,mrs. Scavo.
你好, Scavo太太
That's A...that's a sweet ride.
您的车真不错
Yeah,you think so?
你是这样认为的？
Why don't youcome over here for a second? I'd liketo pick your brain.
为什么不过来一会儿呢? 我想了解一下你的想法
You're the demographicthat my client is interested in,
我的客户对你所在的人群感兴趣
so you'd actuallybe doing me a favor
因此你会帮我一个大忙
if you drove it aroundfor a couple hours,
如果你开着它在转上几个小时
and tell me what you thought.Do you mind?
并告诉我你的想法. 你介意吗?
Are you kidding me?
您不是在开玩笑吧?
I can't believeyou are old enough to drive.
难以置信, 你都到了能驾车的年龄了
I still rememberwhen you were 10 years old.
我仍记得你10岁的时候
I paid you a dollarto rake our leaves.
你为我家耙落叶，我付你1美元
Yeah.
是的
Yeah,you were pretty cheap.
是啊 你才给那么一点儿
is this set up for mp3?
这是mp3装置吗?
Uh,all the bellsand whistles,
哦，是所有铃声和汽笛的
but listen...
听我说...
I really wanted to tell youhow sorry I am.
我想向你表达我的歉意
Hmm?
嗯?
Your lawyercame to see me.
你的律师找过我了
I'm going to be deposed.
我将去作证
It's going to be hardfor me...
对我来说很难办
yeah. Yeah,I know.
是的 我知道
You just have to remember she's a different person
你不要忘了 她只要一喝酒
when she drinks.
就与平时判若两人
She must be.
没错
It's hard for me to imaginethe bree I know capable of hurting you.
我很难想像出 一个忍心打伤你的Bree
Yeah.
是的
Do you have the keys?
你有钥匙吗?
Oh. Sure.
当然有
Anyway,I just...
总之，我
I feel so guilty that thisall went on in your house,
我很内疚 为了你们家发生的事
right under our nose.
发生在你身边的事
So if there is anythingI can do to help you...
如果我能帮上你什么忙...
well,can you geta discount on these?
那么, 这车你可以给我打个折么?
Um...
嗯...
actually,yeah.One of the perks.
那好吧 如果这能使你振作起来的话
Even so,it's a little outof the price range of a high school student.
即便如此, 对于高中生来说 它也超出了可以负担得起的范围
Well,if you tellmy lawyer the truth,
那么, 如果你对律师说出事实
I don't thinkmoney's gonna be a problem.
钱就不再是问题了
hi. What's going on?
你们好 怎么了?
Edie wants to discussour little...
Edie想要声讨我们的
deception.
欺骗行为
Exactly how uglyis this gonna get?
事态会变得很难堪么?
how long does it taketo shut a door?
关个门要费多长时间啊?!
I can forgive your trickery.
我可以原谅你们的诡计
I can forgivethe humiliation.
也能原谅你们对我的侮辱
But what I can't forgive is the completeand
但我不能原谅的是--
utter lack of faith in me!
对我彻底的不信任!
I mean,having susan get marriedfor insurance was my idea!
让Susan结婚以获得保险是我的主意!
Okay,so if I'd knownthat everything had gotten all screwed up,
如果我知道事态有这么严重的话
of course I would've agreed.
我肯定会同意的
Look,edie,in retrospect...
Edie, 当时...
yes,we didn't think.
是的 我们不这么认为
We didn't handle this the way
我们不能像成年人一样
mature adults should have.
来对待这件事
He's right.We behaved like children--
没错 我们表现得像小孩子--
naughty,stupid children.
淘气而愚蠢的小孩
Well,that makes me feel better
你们肯承认这点
that you could admit that.
这使我好受点了
because...
因为...
when naughty children misbehave,
当淘气的小孩做错事的时候
they know that they'regonna get punished. Don't they?
他们知道自己会受罚 不是吗?
Punished?
受罚?
At this point,I'd like to point out that, uh,it was karl who proposed.
既然如此, 我想说明 是Karl求婚的
Karl.
You are gonna throw mean elaborate wedding.
你要为我准备一个精致的婚礼
Yes,of course.
当然了
Anything,baby.
做什么都可以, 亲爱的
How elaborate?
有多精致?
Well,figure out exactly whatit is that you could afford,
精确算出你实际能负担得起多少钱
and triple it.
将它乘以三
As for you--
至于你...
okay,now remember,I'm broke.
Ok, 不过, 我可是一文不名的
I'm well awareof your church mouse status.
我也知道你没钱
I don't intendto lift a finger
在这个无比精致婚礼的
during the planningand execution
准备和执行期间
of this crushingly expensive wedding.
我什么都不想操心
No. No,of course not.
是的 当然不用
And anythingI can do to help...
如果我能帮上任何忙...
uh,you know,I would--I couldhelp with the engagement party.
你知道, 我可以帮忙举办你的订婚宴会
How's that?
那又怎样?
Well,I wasn't planningon inviting you.
我没打算邀请你参加
But...
但是...
I will need a bartender.
我需要一位酒吧招待
Oh,oh,and,um...
噢 嗯...
make sure you come inthrough the back door.
你必须由后门进
You're just in time.
你来得真及时
Mrs. Scavo has been sworn in,
Scavo太太刚宣了誓
so we're all ready to start.
我们可以正式开始了
Hey.
嗨
All right,we are now on the record.
我们所说的将被记录在案
Okay.
好的
Isn't it true that while yourchildren were in bree's care,
Bree在照看你孩子的时候
that she passed out drunk and allowed them to wander off
是否喝醉到不省人事 让孩子们走迷了路
to a downtown business district?
最后走到城市商业区去了?
My kids don't wander.They scurry,like rats.
他们不是迷路 他们像老鼠一样到处乱窜
Excuse me?
能再说一遍吗?
Do you know a ratcan fit through a hole the size of a quarter?
您知道吗? 只要有硬币大小的洞 老鼠就能钻进去
Anyway,my childrenhave that trick down,too.
总之, 我孩子们的诡计成功了
Mrs. Scavo,are you saying that you don't holdmrs.
Scavo太太, 你认为Van De Kamp太太
Van de kamp responsible for endangeringyour children?
对你的孩子陷入险境没有责任?
No,I don'thold her responsible.
是的 我认为她没有责任
Bree van de kamp and I haveknown each other a long time.
Bree Van De Kamp和我认识很久了
I trust her completely.
我完全信任她
She's a wonderful friendand a fantastic mother.
她是值得信赖的朋友和完美的母亲
She puts the rest of usto shame.
我们都为赶不上她而感到羞愧
She's lying!
她在撒谎!
Are you gonnalet her get away with this crap?
你不让她带着这些废话离开这儿吗?
please.
请别说了
do you consider mrs. Van de kampto have a drinking problem?
你认为Van De Kamp太太有酗酒问题吗?
No.
不
Then why did you lineempty wine bottles up on her front stoop?
那你为什么在她家前门平台上 将酒瓶摆放成一排?
I was helping breewith her recycling.
我在帮助Bree回收废品
Do I need to remind you of the potential consequencesof perjury?
我需要提醒你作伪证的后果吗?
No,you don'T.In fact,I hate liars.
不需要 实际上我痛恨撒谎者
hello?
你好
Peter. Hi,
Peter 你好
it's bree.
我是Bree
Hey,bree.You know,um,
你好, Bree, 你知道的
if you feel likeyou're gonna need a drink,
如果你又想喝酒了
you should call donna.
你应该给Donna打电话
No! No,I-I don't feel likeI'm gonna drink.
不! 我并不想喝酒
And if I did,I certainly would call donna.
如果我想的话, 我肯定会电话给Donna的
I mean,she and I are just... we're just really clicking.
我的意思是, 她和我... 挺合得来的
Oh,that's good.So why are you calling?
不错啊 那你为什么打这个电话呢?
I know it's really late notice, but a friend of mine,uh,
我知道这有点迟了 不过我有个朋友
got engagedand she's throwing a party, and I thought,um,
她订婚了, 要举办一个聚会 我认为--
maybe you'd like to come.
你可能会愿意参加
Bree...
well,you're notmy sponsor anymore, so I assumethis is allowable.
你不再是我的互助伙伴了 我认为参加聚会是可以的
I mean,it's justa casual get-together.
只是非正式的聚一下
And they're having sushi.You do like sushi, don't you?
而且有寿司吃 你不是很喜欢吃寿司吗?
Bree...
okay,peter,I just really...
Ok, Peter 我只是
need us to be friends.
想跟你做朋友而已
When I'm with you,I'm not myself, which is a good thing.
跟你在一起时，我不再是我自己 这是一件好事
I can...
我能...
I can relaxwhen I'm with you
跟你在一起时我能放松
in a way that I can'twhen I'm with other people.
而跟别人一起的时候我是做不到的
with them,I have to pretendthat I have it all together,but...
我必须假装自己什么都好 但是...
you know that I don't, so it's just so much easier.
你知道我并非如此 这样做对我来说只是更容易些
Come on,it's just A...
过来吧 这只是
it's justa dumb old party.
一个聚会而已, 没什么大不了的
Bree...
do not call me again.
不要再给我打电话了
Paul!I am so glad you made it.
Paul! 你过来我很高兴
I appreciatethe invitation,edie.
很感谢你的邀请, Edie
Although,frankly, I'm a littlesurprised to get it
尽管坦白说,鉴于街坊邻居们对我的印象
considering how people in this neighborhood feel about me.
接到邀请我很意外
Oh. You know me.I like to be inclusive.
你知道, 我不愿漏请任何人
Ooh! It's heavy.
噢! 很沉啊
uh,unh-unh.This is flat.
啊 淡而无味
I think I'd like,um...
我想要...
a rusty nail.
一杯Rust Nail(酒名)
A what now?
什么?
It's a cocktail, well,I'm not really surewhat's in it.
鸡尾酒的一种 但我不知道怎么调制
But it sounds obscureand complicated, so chop-chop.
似乎挺难的 快干活去吧
be right there.
在那
hey,hey. Put that down.We gotta go.
嘿 放下那个 我们得走了
Our birth mother just went into labor.
孩子的生母快要分娩了
-What?
- 什么?
That's fantastic!
太棒了!
Yeah,can you believe it? We're gonna be parents.
是的 你相信吗? 我们要做父母了
I'll go get the car.Come on.
我去开车 走吧
We were supposed to havefour weeks.
预计还有4周的时间啊
She promised me the babywasn't due for four more weeks.
她说婴儿4周后才出生
We don't have anything! We don't--we don't have diapers,
我们什么都没准备! 没有尿布
and we don't havethe stuff babies drink.
婴儿饮品也没有
-Formula.
- 方案
Exactly. We're not ready!
没错 还没准备好呢!
You know,this isa total inconvenience.
你知道, 这有很多不便
Welcome to parenthood.Come on.
恭喜你们获得了父母身份 快点
This isyour father's bartender bible.
这是你父亲的酒吧招待百科全书
See if you can find a recipe for a rusty nail.Okay.
看你能否找到Rust Nail的调制方法
Um,mom?
呃, 妈妈?
Where'd you find that?
你在哪找到的?
It was stuck in here between a pink squirreland a pisco sour.
它就塞在Pink Squirrel 和Pisco Sour之间
Oh.
噢
Well,why is your fatherkeeping this?
你爸爸为什么保存着这个?
Why do you think?
你觉得为什么?
Hey,susie.
你好啊, Susie
Karl,this marriage--our marriage,
Karl, 这次婚姻--我们这次
this fake marriage, that's what it is,right?Fake.
是假结婚, 对吗? 假的
-What are youtalking about?
- 你在说什么?
What's this?
这是什么?
Nothing.
什么也不是
Yeah?
是吗?
Okay,then,
Ok 那么,
repeat after me.
重复我的话
"Our marriage is fake,
"我们是假结婚"
"and I'm going to marrythe woman i really love--edie britt."
"我将和我的真爱--Edie Britt结婚"
If that's whatyou want me to say.
如果那是你想让我说这些
No,no,no,no! It's not about what i want you to say.
不, 不是的! 与我想让你说无关
You have to want to say
你必须发自肺腑地说
that you want to marry edie.
你想娶Edie
Don't worryabout this,susie.
别担心这个, Susie
Why are youhanging on to that?
为什么你还留着呢?
I need to look at itfrom time to time.
我需要不时地看看它
Why?
为什么?
consider it my punishment.
把这当成是对我的惩罚
For screwing up the best thing
破坏了上天赐予我的
that ever happened to me.
最好幸福
Oh. Oh,no,no,no.This is not happening.
噢 不是的 没这回事
Oh,karl!
噢, Karl!
Oh! Will you--
噢! 你会--
are you crazy?!
你疯了吗?!
Just tell mewhat to do,susie.
告诉我该怎么做, Susie.
If you want meto marry edie,I will.You want me to call offthe wedding,I'll do it.
如果你想让我娶Edie, 我会的 如果你想让我取消婚礼,我也会的
I'll do whatever you want. I'm putty.
你让我做什么我都愿意 我为你癫狂
-karl!
- Karl!
Whoa!
哇!
what are you doing?
你在干什么?
I'm,just,uh,putting away some coats.
我在把这些衣服放好
Oh.
噢
Well,it's timeto open my presents.
差不多该拆礼物了
Let's go.
走吧
oh,hello.
你好
-Hi.
- 你好
Hi. Um,
你好
I need some advicefrom a professional.
我需要一位专家的建议
I'd liketo get stinking drunk.
我想要喝的酩酊大醉
Do you have anything thatcan accomplish that in a hurry?
你有什么能快速办到的方法吗?
I forgot the lamaze bookin my purse!
我忘了提包里的那本心理助产书!
Oh,forget it. Come on.Let's go. We'll wing it.
没关系 走吧 我们即兴发挥也可以
Oh,we missed it!
哦, 我们错过了!
the kidjust slipped right out.
孩子就这样"溜"出来了
Are you family?
你们是亲属吗?
They're the parents.
他们是孩子的"父母"
would you like to help?
想过来帮忙吗?
No,thanks.
不用了, 谢谢
You guys look likeyou got it covered.
看来你们差不多快裹好了
Oh,are you sure,honey?
你确定不过来吗, 亲爱的?
Come on,gaby.
过来吧, Gaby.
I just,um...
我, 呃...
I-I don't wanna do anythingto screw it up.
不想给你们添乱而已
She won't break.
不会的
here.
过这来
Okay.
好的
hi.
你好
Hi.
Oh,honey,you were right.
亲爱的, 你是正确的
About what?
关于什么?
It was all worth it.
付出这么多确实值得
serving bowls.
餐具
Just what I needed,lynette.
这正是我想要的, Lynette
There's a gift receipttaped to the bottom of the box.
礼盒底部是它的收据
Oh. thank god!
噢 天哪!
Okay,the next oneis from felicia.
OK 下一个礼物是Felicia的
I do hope you like it.
我真希望你能喜欢
Oh,you knowwhat they say--
人们常说
good thingscome in small packages.
小包裹里往往是好东西
what is it?
这是什么?
Teeth?
牙齿?
Dentures.
一副假牙
they weremy dear sister martha'S.
它们是我亲爱的姐姐Martha的
I'm sure none of you knew,
我确定你们都不知道
but she had orthodontic issues from the timeshe was a child.
她从孩提时代开始就有畸齿的问题
Oh.
噢
thank you.
谢谢
I know it's an unconventional gift for an engagement party,
我知道这礼物对于订婚典礼来说不合传统
but you and martha were such close friends,edie.
但你和Martha曾经是 如此亲密的朋友, Edie
I wanted you to have something truly personal to remember her by,
我希望你能拥有一件 让你永远记住她的私人礼物
since she left us so...
因为她就这样
abruptly.
匆匆离去
You know,
你知道
when paul young strangled her, crushed her windpipe
当Paul Young紧紧扼住她 捏碎她的喉管
and buried her alive next to a garbage-strewnhiking trail.
并将她活埋在洒满垃圾的小径旁
Felicia,uh...I think you've had enough.
Felicia, 呃... 我认为你说得够多了
I do apologizeif I've offended anyone,but...
如果我有冒犯之处, 我道歉 但是...
while you allare chitchatting and eatingthese gummy hors d'oeuvres,
当你们所有人一起闲聊 食用这些粘粘的开胃食品之时
just remember...
别忘了...
you're in the companyof a murderer.
一个杀人犯就陪伴在你们身边
Bree?
why didn't you call donna?
为什么不给Donna打电话呢?
I don't need donna.
我不需要Donna.
I need you.
我需要你.
You know,I don't even like redheads.
你知道, 我不喜欢红发女子
okay,it's my turn.
Ok, 轮到我了
Shh. In a minute.
嘘 等会儿
Come on,you're hogging her.
给我吧, 别想独占她
tell me!
告诉我!
You tell me who it is,libby.
告诉我这是怎么回事, Libby.
are you drunk?
你喝醉了?
Who is he,libby? Hmm?
孩子的父亲是谁, Libby?
I got to know.
我必须得知道
I already told you,he's just some rodeo guy.
我告诉过你了, 他是个参加牛仔竞技的人
I don't even remember his name.
我连他的名字都不记得了
Liar!
撒谎!
what are you doing?
你在干什么?
I am gonnalight myself on fire.
我要自焚!
He's gonna light himself on fire with coffee liqueur?
他要用咖啡利口酒自焚?
Would nothave been my choice.
要是我，才不这么做呢
Tell me his name,or I'm gonna do it!
告诉我他叫什么名字 不然我真的要点火了
Frank,you're being an idiot.
Frank, 你真是个白痴
Aah! Aah!
嗷! 嗷!
It was dale,okay?It was dale.
是Dale, OK? 是Dale
My brother dale?
我弟弟Dale?
He's a kid!
他只是个孩子!
Well,he's 19,frank. He knows which end is up.
他已经19岁了, Frank. 懂得很多事情
Wait,what is she saying?
等会, 她在说什么?
there's a father.
孩子的生父
Hey! Hey!
嘿! 嘿!
-no.
- 不
leave me alone!
放开我!
I'm notgiving up the baby.
我不会放弃这个婴儿的
Let's get him out of here.
把他带走
No! No!
不! 不!
What the hellare you doing?
你究竟在做什么
Taking our baby home.
把我们的孩子带回家
She's not ours. The papers aren't valid anymore.
孩子不是我们的 文件现在没有法律效力了
She has a father.
生父冒出来了
Do you really wanna leave this beautiful little girl
你真的想让这个可爱的小女孩
with thatwhite trash freak show?!
留下来看那个垃圾表演的闹剧?!
Huh?
啊?
Well,come on,then.
那么咱们走
-where?
- 去哪?
Maternity. Maternity.
妇产科 妇产科
All right.
好吧
Hurry up!
快点!
I'm hurrying.
我已经很快了
man,there's a lotof straps on this thing!
这东西的捆绑带太多了
How does this thing go in?
怎么弄啊?
Read the instructions!
看说明书!
"Pass strap 'a'through strap 'b,'
"将皮带'a'穿过'b'
making sure that the harnessclip is at the chest level."
确保皮带扣在胸腔的位置"
Well,which damn one is the harness clip?
这该死的皮带扣在哪?
That is after the baby is in.
把孩子放上去以后再扣
You have to connect itto the car first!
你需要先将座椅固定在车上!
I told youwe should've got an S.U.V.!
我早跟你说过我们应该买一辆S.U.V.!
Okay,stop yelling!This is very complicated.
OK, 别叫了! 这很复杂的
Oh,for god's sakes.Just take the baby.
看在上帝的份上 看好孩子
Wow.
哇
We're good to go. Give me the baby.
我们准备好了 把孩子给我
you knowthis isn't gonna end well.
你知道这不会有什么好结果的
You know,they're just gonnatry and take her back.
他们会拚命要回这孩子
maybe.
也许吧
But we don'thave to make it easy for them.
但我们也不会让他们轻易得逞
-Gaby,I--
- Gaby, 我--
look,just buckle up!
系好安全带!
temptation comes to all of us.
所有人都受到诱惑
Whether or not we succumb
我们是否臣服于诱惑
depends on our ability to recognize its disguise.
在于我们识别其伪装的能力
Sometimes it arrives in the form of an old flame,
有时候它以旧火花的形式出现
flickering back to life.
重回生活中闪耀
Or a new friend
或者一个新朋友
who could end up being so much more.
对我们意义更深
Or a young child
或者一个新生命
who awakens feelings we didn't know we had.
触发了我们以为自己不可能拥有的情感
And so we give in to temptation,
因此我们屈从于诱惑
all the while knowing come morning,
至始至终都知道之后
we'll have to suffer the consequences.
我们必须承担的后果